[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the single parent family in the dramatic movie Pay It Forward?", "correct_answer": "McKinney", "incorrect_answers": ["Travis", "Wellington", "Parkinson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A starfish cannot regenerate a lost arm.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the first Filipino-American to become Governor of a US state?", "correct_answer": "Benjamin Cayetano", "incorrect_answers": ["Franklin  Rakata", "Jose Nisperos", "Jose Rizal"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What term derives from a Latin word meaning rods bundled around an axe ?", "correct_answer": "Fascism", "incorrect_answers": ["Despot", "Caesar", "Sovereign"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Snakes consume their food by means of this process.", "correct_answer": "Swallowing", "incorrect_answers": ["Breathing", "Absorption", "Chewing"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 2000 movie The Perfect Storm, what is the name of the bar where the crew hangs out when not at sea?", "correct_answer": "The Crows Nest", "incorrect_answers": ["The Shipwreck", "The Poopdeck", "The Wheelhouse"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is an endothermic chemical reaction?", "correct_answer": "A chemical reaction in which energy is used up", "incorrect_answers": ["A chemical reaction in which energy is released", "A chemical reaction in which oxides are produced", "A chemical reaction in which carbon compounds are involved"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Carmen: A Hip Hopera , what do the tarot cards of the fortune teller read for Carmen?", "correct_answer": "Death", "incorrect_answers": ["Happiness", "Tears", "Fame"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A large number of flies can appear around a dead body within the first 24 hours of death.  This is mainly because the flies lay eggs on the body, this multiplying their numbers.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these procedures is done as a form of ear shaping, which often results in a non-human appearance of the ear?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Pointing", "Amputation", "Cutting and cropping"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Mel Gibson played Gabriel in the movie The Patriot.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which country was not among the founding states of the European Economic Community (the European Union predecessor)?", "correct_answer": "UK", "incorrect_answers": ["Luxembourg", "Italy", "France"]}]